<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prologue on</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in Prologue on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/introduction/</guid><description>Currently, KubeDL supports running TensorFlow, PyTorch, XGBoost, Mars and MPI distributed training jobs on Kubernetes.
Introduction Key Features Support different kinds of deep learning training jobs in a single controller. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to run each controller for each job kind. Expose unified prometheus metrics for job stats. Persist job metadata and events in external storage such as Mysql or certain event DB to outlive api-server state.</description></item><item><title>Install Using Helm</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/install-using-helm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 16:47:24 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/install-using-helm/</guid><description>Install Helm Helm is a package manager for Kubernetes. You can install helm with command below on MacOS
brew install helm Check the helm website for more details.
Install KubeDL From the root directory, run
helm install kubedl ./helm/kubedl --create-namespace -n kubedl-system You can override default values defined in values.yaml with --set flag. For example, set the custom cpu/memory resource:
helm install kubedl ./helm/kubedl --create-namespace -n kubedl-system --set resources.</description></item><item><title>Install Using Yaml</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/install-using-yaml/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 17:46:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/install-using-yaml/</guid><description>Install CRDs From project root directory, run
kubectl apply -f config/crd/bases/ Install KubeDL controller A single yaml file including everything: deployment, rbac etc.
kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kubedl-io/kubedl/master/config/manager/all_in_one.yaml KubeDL controller is installed under kubedl-system namespace.
The official KubeDL controller image is hosted under docker hub.
Uninstall KubeDL controller kubectl delete namespace kubedl-system Delete CRDs kubectl get crd | grep kubedl.io | cut -d ' ' -f 1 | xargs kubectl delete crd Enable specific job Kind KubeDL supports all kinds of jobs(tensorflow, pytorch etc.</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/quick-start/</guid><description>Submit the TensorFlow job kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/alibaba/kubedl/v0.3.0/example/tf/tf_job_mnist.yaml Get job status kubectl get tfjobs -n kubedl kubectl describe tfjob mnist -n kubedl Delete the job kubectl delete tfjob mnist -n kubedl Other commands Commands →</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/commands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://kubedl.io/docs/prologue/commands/</guid><description>Training Job kind tfjob pytorchjob marsjob mpijob xdljob elasticdljob xgboostjob Other Workload Kind cron These kinds can be used in the kubectl command.
Submit kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/alibaba/kubedl/v0.3.0/example/tf/tf_job_mnist.yaml List kubectl get tfjobs -n kubedl Get kubectl describe tfjob mnist -n kubedl Delete kubectl delete tfjob mnist -n kubedl</description></item></channel></rss>