<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contributing on</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/contributing/</link><description>Recent content in Contributing on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:03 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kubedl.io/docs/contributing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Contribute</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/contributing/how-to-contribute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 17:22:54 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kubedl.io/docs/contributing/how-to-contribute/</guid><description>Contributing to KubeDL Welcome to KubeDL! We encourage you to help out by reporting issues, improving documentation, fixing bugs, or adding new features. Please also take a look at our code of conduct, which details how contributors are expected to conduct themselves as part of the KubeDL community.
Reporting issues To be honest, we regard every user of KubeDL as a very kind contributor. After experiencing KubeDL, you may have some feedback for the project.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 14:54:39 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kubedl.io/docs/contributing/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description></item><item><title>Comparisons</title><link>https://kubedl.io/docs/contributing/comparisons/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 14:54:39 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://kubedl.io/docs/contributing/comparisons/</guid><description>Comparisons with Kubeflow KubeDL supports training, modeling lineage versioning, inference, and automatic tuning for model deployment on Kubernetes. Kubeflow is a machine learning toolkit for Kubernetes that contains several projects for different purposes.
Both projects share the same goal to enable machine learning run on Kubernetes, but largely solve different problems, or in different approaches, or can complement each other in this area.
KubeDL modeling lineage and versioning: KubeDL tracks the history of a model in the native Kubernetes CRD format which is unique and easy for existing Kubernetes users to adopt and can leverage broad Kubernetes tooling ecosystem.</description></item></channel></rss>